dafun.io 2016-11-27

# Privacy Policy - dafun.io

#### General

DaFun is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our information-gathering and dissemination practices for our service. By using our services, you acknowledge that you have reviewed this Privacy Policy and agree to be bound by their terms and conditions. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of entities DaFun does not own or control, or to individuals whom DaFun does not employ or manage, including any third parties to whom DaFun may disclose Personal Information (as defined below) pursuant to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

#### DATA AND PERSONAL INFORMATION

1\. Registration Information With respect to users who voluntarily register to our services (by logging in to their Facebook account), DaFun may collect personally-identifying information that is unique to such users (such as their name, profile picture, gender, internet protocol (IP) address and Facebook friend list. 

#### 2\. Other information 

We also receive and/or collect other types of data and information about users via our services, as follows: 

• We regularly receive non-personally-identifying information about you or about the device you use to enhance our services, such as your browser type, language preference referring site and any other information automatically sent to DaFun by the user's browser. 

• We receive data about you whenever you use or interact with DaFun, such as how and when you view, use or otherwise interact with content and materials in our WebSite. For example, we may infer data from your replies and answers to the quizzes in this WebSite or the results thereof, as further delineated below. 

• When you post or create content on DaFun, such as feedbacks, quizzes or other games, we may receive additional related data (or metadata), such as the time, date, and place you posted or created such content. 

• Sometimes we get data from our partners, publishers, commercial customers and other third parties that helps us (or them) deliver ads, understand our users' online activities, provide with insight into what our users are interested in, maximize the effectiveness of ads, and generally make our services better. 

We store data for as long as it is necessary to provide products and services to you and others (including those described hereunder), but some information may remain in backup copies and logs for longer periods. However, you acknowledge and agree that We may continue to use any non-personally-identifying information in accordance with this Privacy Policy (e.g., for the purpose of analysis, statistics and the like) also after the termination of your membership to this website and\or use of our services, for any reason whatsoever. 

#### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We use the information and data we collect in connection with operation, maintenance and enhancement of our services and features, and for other administrative purposes or internal operations, such as communicating with our users, data analysis, testing and research. In addition, We may use the information and data we collect about you in order to measure and understand the effectiveness of our ads and other content and offer you tailored content, like giving you more relevant ads. For example, your birthday, gender and other demographic characteristics allow us to show you age-appropriate and gender-related content and advertisements. We may also examine and analyze your feedback and answers to the quizzes in our WebSite to serve ads that you may enjoy or find interesting. For example, if a user participates in content around new model cars, We may infer that this user is planning to purchase a new vehicle or that he/she recently purchased a new vehicle. Alternatively, if a user indicates in a quiz that he/she enjoys baseball, We may infer this user is a sport fan. Advertisers of either automotive or sports products may ask us to display advertisements to individuals that have an affinity towards their products. DaFun processes Personal Information on its servers in many countries around the world. Such information may be stored on any of our servers, at any location. 

#### SHARING OF INFORMATION

Except as described hereunder, We do not share your Personal Information with third parties unless We have received your permission to do so, or given you notice thereof (such as by telling you about it in this Privacy Policy), or removed your name and any other personally identifying information from it. For example, We may inform our advertisers and publishers how their ads perform or how many users viewed or clicked on their ads. We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those set out in this Privacy Policy. 

1\. Sharing of Personal Information in the WebSite 

Some features of the services allow users to post contents and materials in, and create quizzes and other games through, the Website, as further delineated in our EULA. Any contents, materials and games which you have publicly posted or published on the WebSite or otherwise through our services shall be publicly available by default, and you may appear in the WebSite as the creator thereof. In addition, the username, the full name and the profile picture of any user who shall voluntary register to our services, as well as the list of recently played games by such user, shall be publicly available in the WebSite. 

2\. Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement 

DaFun may identify a user to third parties and/or share your information (including your Personal Information) if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that disclosing such information is necessary to comply with any law, regulation or other governmental authority, or respond to any court order, subpoena, search warrant or equivalent, or where in our reasonable belief an action is needed in order to protect the safety or security of any personal or property. DaFun also reserves the right to disclose any information in case it believes, in good faith, that such disclosure is appropriate or necessary in order to enforce our EULA, take precautions against liabilities, investigate and defend itself against any third party claims or allegations, assist government enforcement agencies, protect the security or integrity of the WebSite and our servers and protect the rights and property, of DaFun, its users and\or others. 

3\. Non-Personal Aggregate Information 

DaFun may publish or share with third parties aggregate information for the purpose of analysis and statistics. Such disclosure is done anonymously and is non-personally identifiable. For example, we may share information publicly to show trends about the general use of our services. 

4\. Cookies 

A cookie is a string of information that can be stored on your computer (if your web browser is set to permit storage of cookies). We may use such cookies to help us learn about how you use this WebSite, user demographics and enhance your online experience. Users can install Google analytics Opt-out Browser add-on to prevent their data from being used by Google Analytics. (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) 

5\. Reorganization or Insolvency 

DaFun may also transfer Personal Information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation, change of control or other corporate reorganization in which DaFun participates, or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of DaFun's shares or assets to which the WebSite relates. In the event of a bankruptcy, insolvency or equivalents, DaFun may not be able to control how your Personal Information is handled, shared or used. However, in all such events, We will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such third parties from disclosing your Personal Information. 

OTHER WEBSITES AND SERVICES

We are not responsible for the practices employed by any websites or services linked to or from DaFun, including the information or content contained within them. Please be aware that if you choose to use a link to go from DaFun to any third party's website or service, such third party's own rules and privacy policy (and not our Privacy Policy) will apply and govern your activities and any information you disclose while interacting with such third parties. Therefore, We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your Personal Information, and you acknowledge and agree that We are not responsible for any wrongful use or disclosure made by such third parties, and that We do not have control over such third-parties. If you are using a third-party's website or service and you allow them to access your Personal Information and user content you do so at your own risk. 

E-MAIL COMMUNICATIONS

If you are a registered user of DaFun and have supplied us your email address, you may occasionally receive emails from us relating to your account, or with respect to updates on new features or other changes in the WebSite, or for customer service purposes, or otherwise as shall be required in order to enable your use of our services. 

SECURITY

All information described above may be stored on database servers. We will take commercially reasonable measures in providing secure transmission of your Personal Information before it is transferred across the internet from your system to our servers and in securing such Personal Information stored on our systems. However, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the internet and that there is also some risk that others could find a way to thwart our security systems. As a result, while We strive to protect your Personal Information, We cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of your Personal Information or other content you transmit using DaFun, and you do so at your own risk. Thus, We encourage you to exercise discretion regarding the Personal Information you choose to disclose. 

PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES

DaFun reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time, with or without notice. If so, DaFun will post its updated Privacy Policy on its WebSite. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of our services will be subject to the then-current privacy policy. If any modification is unacceptable to you, you may cease using our services. If you do not cease using our services, you will be deemed to have accepted those modifications.
